{"data":[{"question":"Please would you to send me further details, of the job advertised?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Please","b":"to send","c":"further","d":"advertised","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To send-> send","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Children learn a lot about how to behave in a situation as this.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"about","b":"to behave","c":"in","d":"as","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- As->like","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"I write to his almost every day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"write","b":"to","c":"his","d":"almost","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- His-> him","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Even though I admire his courage, I think he has been foolish.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Even though","b":"admire","c":"think","d":"has been","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Has been-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"We would get the job finished much quicker if everyone worked as hardly as everyone else.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would get","b":"much quicker","c":"as hardly as","d":"everyone else","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- As hardly as-> as hard as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"One of the patients in a local hospital has one typhoid.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"patients","b":"in","c":"local","d":"one","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- One->x\nBefore the diseases name, 'Article' is not used","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"I think cycling is preferable with walking.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"cycling","b":"preferable","c":"with","d":"walking","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- With-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"He said he disapproved of people which smoked.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"said","b":"disapproved","c":"of","d":"which","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Which-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"You can't possible expect me to have supper ready by 8 o'clock.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"possible","b":"expect","c":"to have","d":"ready","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Possible-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"I had been looking for this book for months and at last I have found it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had been","b":"for","c":"at last","d":"have found","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Had been-> has been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}